2000: Man...
XP: Hm?
2000: What are we gonna do now?
XP: It's been quiet lately.
2000: Yeah.
2000: I don't feel good nowadays.
2000: Especially after their deaths.
XP: Sigh...
XP: It's all of the sudden, too.
2000: I don't understand.
2000: Why does it have to be now?
XP: I would tell if I knew.
2000: It doesn't add up.
XP: Look, neither of us know everything.
XP: But we know they're doing well.
2000: Yeah, perhaps more than we do.
XP: Are we in the right to know everything?
2000: Well, no...
2000: Ugh.
XP: I'm sorry, 2000.
XP: I know it isn't easy.
XP: At least we rest assured knowing they're fine.
XP: Plus, Vista will be here, too.
2000: I guess so.
2000: Thanks, though.
XP: Oh yeah, that reminds me.
XP: Wanna check out my PC build?
2000: Oh, right!
2000: I forgot you finished building.
2000: I'm up for it.
XP: Alright, let's go then!
XP: Here we are!
XP: Let's enter.
2000: Oh wow.
2000: You've done quite the work here.
XP: Yeah, I got it all cleaned up.
XP: The PC's in my room now.
2000: Right. Let's go there then.
2000: Woah.
2000: Quite a build you have there.
XP: Yep!
XP: With a little topping from the decade before.
2000: I see that.
XP: Anyways, here are the specs...
XP: Athlon 64 X2 AM2+ CPU
XP: Gigabyte GA-M51GM-S2G motherboard
XP: 600W Cooler Master power supply
XP: Inwin A500 AT PC case
XP: NVIDIA GeForce 7800 GTX GPU
XP: And some other components, of course.
2000: How?
2000: How did you get all this?
XP: Could be from anywhere.
XP: You never know!
2000: This is just impressive.
2000: How much did it even cost?
XP: I'd say a grand.
2000: You are out of your mind!
XP: I mean, I heard a legend that PCs were about $3,000 before, so...
2000: Where did you hear that from?
XP: I don't know.
XP: Kind of forgot where I heard that...
2000: Hmm.
XP: Anyway, I have some games on the PC.
XP: Wanna play?
2000: Sure!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Okay, what’s going on today?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: There’s been no customers.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: No 98 either...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Whatever. It's getting late.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I'm gonna close.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: What a beautiful sunset.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Nothing quite like Vienna Park, huh.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I wonder what the two are up to now...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Huh?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: What's this?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Looks like a Pocket PC...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Did someone drop it?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: It's not turning on...
Longhorn: Ubuntu?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Oh, hey Longhorn.
Longhorn: What are you doing?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I just found this phone on the ground.
Longhorn: Odd.
Longhorn: Someone must've dropped it.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Yeah.
Longhorn: Wait a second...
Longhorn: This is 98's!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: How do you know?
Longhorn: The screen is cracked.
Longhorn: I remember seeing him use it in my shop.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: You don't suppose someone dropped it?
Longhorn: Yeah, but it smells fishy.
Longhorn: Did I tell you no icons came over today?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: You... What?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I had no customers in my shop today.
Longhorn: You're joking...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Not just a coincidence, is it...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Can we at least return the phone?
Longhorn: Yeah. Let's do that.
Longhorn: Okay, where to?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: What about the door?
Longhorn: Oh, yeah.
Longhorn: It's locked.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Sigh.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Should we just go back?
Longhorn: What are we gonna do with the phone?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Right...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: How about we leave it here?
Longhorn: That's dangerous.
Longhorn: Especially given today's... Oddities.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Okay... Yeah.
Longhorn: Wait, let's check the surroundings.
Longhorn: We might find some way to get in.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: That's ridiculous.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: You want to break in to his house?
Longhorn: Well, there's no other way...
Longhorn: The sun's setting as well...